{
    "subject":"Government",
    "topics":
    [
        {
            "topic":"Apathy",
            "questions":
            [
                {
                    "question":"Types of apathy include all except",
                    "opt1":"political",
                    "opt2":"religious",
                    "opt3":"agricultural",
                    "opt4":"participation",
                    "ans":"participation"
                },
                {
                    "question":"Apathy is synonymous with",
                    "opt1":"Indifference",
                    "opt2":"Similar",
                    "opt3":"Participation",
                    "opt4":"Culture",
                    "ans":"Indifference"
                },

                {
                    "question":"Political apathy means",
                    "opt1":"the indifference to politics",
                    "opt2":"the similarities between politics",
                    "opt3":"the participation in politics",
                    "opt4":"the culture of politics",
                    "ans":"the indifference to politics"
                },
                {
                    "question":"Apathy is known world-wide",
                    "opt1":"True",
                    "opt2":"False",
                    "opt3":"Maybe",
                    "opt4":"I don't know",
                    "ans":"True"
                },
                {
                    "question":"People have the right to apathy",
                    "opt1":"True",
                    "opt2":"False",
                    "opt3":"Maybe",
                    "opt4":"I don't know",
                    "ans":"True"
                },
                {
                    "question":"Political apathy improves the political system of the country",
                    "opt1":"True",
                    "opt2":"False",
                    "opt3":"Maybe",
                    "opt4":"I don't know",
                    "ans":"False"
                }
                
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic":"Sovereignty",
            "questions":
            [
                {
                    "question":"sovereignty means",
                    "opt1":"independence",
                    "opt2":"active",
                    "opt3":"social",
                    "opt4":"deprived",
                    "ans":"independence"
                },
                {
                    "question":"example of a sovereign state is except",
                    "opt1":"Nigeria",
                    "opt2":"USA",
                    "opt3":"Nairobi",
                    "opt4":"Ikeja",
                    "ans":"Ikeja"
                },

                {
                    "question":"an importance of sovereignty is",
                    "opt1":"it makes one or a state immune to external influence",
                    "opt2":"it helps to be safe",
                    "opt3":"it prevents killing",
                    "opt4":"it promotes violence",
                    "ans":"it makes one or a state immune to external influence"
                },
                {
                    "question":"a sovereign state could be in charge of its external affairs",
                    "opt1":"True",
                    "opt2":"False",
                    "opt3":"Maybe",
                    "opt4":"I don't know",
                    "ans":"True"
                },
                {
                    "question":"can the president of a state be sovereign",
                    "opt1":"True",
                    "opt2":"False",
                    "opt3":"Maybe",
                    "opt4":"I don't know",
                    "ans":"True"
                },
                {
                    "question":"beign sovereign is not popular among the asian continent",
                    "opt1":"True",
                    "opt2":"False",
                    "opt3":"Maybe",
                    "opt4":"I don't know",
                    "ans":"False"
                }
                
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic":"Constitution",
            "questions":
            [
                {
                    "question":"The rigid constitution is usually written",
                    "opt1":"True",
                    "opt2":"False",
                    "opt3":"Maybe",
                    "opt4":"I don't know",
                    "ans":"True"
                },
                {
                    "question":"One of these is a source of the constitution",
                    "opt1":"judicial precedents",
                    "opt2":"tenure of the government",
                    "opt3":"citizenship",
                    "opt4":"power",
                    "ans":"judicial precedents"
                },

                {
                    "question":"The preamble is not a feature of the constitution",
                    "opt1":"True",
                    "opt2":"False",
                    "opt3":"Maybe",
                    "opt4":"I don't know",
                    "ans":"False"
                },
                {
                    "question":"Nigeria operates on what type of constitution",
                    "opt1":"written",
                    "opt2":"unwritten",
                    "opt3":"rigid",
                    "opt4":"flexible",
                    "ans":"written"
                },
                {
                    "question":"A constitution defines the power of the arms and tiers of government",
                    "opt1":"True",
                    "opt2":"False",
                    "opt3":"Maybe",
                    "opt4":"I don't know",
                    "ans":"True"
                },
                {
                    "question":"A flexible constitution means",
                    "opt1":"it is unwritten",
                    "opt2":"it is based on tiers of government",
                    "opt3":"it is easy to ammend",
                    "opt4":"it is hard to define",
                    "ans":"it is easy to ammend"
                }
                
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic":"Basic Principles of Government",
            "questions":
            [
                {
                    "question":"The rule of law was proposed by",
                    "opt1":"A.V Dicey",
                    "opt2":"Lord Lugard",
                    "opt3":"Aristotle",
                    "opt4":"Kentucky",
                    "ans":"A.V Dicey"
                },
                {
                    "question":"Rule of law means",
                    "opt1":"No one is above the law",
                    "opt2":"There is a law for everyone",
                    "opt3":"Rules applicable to law",
                    "opt4":"The law and its components",
                    "ans":"No one is above the law"
                },

                {
                    "question":"All of these are principles of rule of law except",
                    "opt1":"equality",
                    "opt2":"impartiality",
                    "opt3":"individual rights",
                    "opt4":"privilleged",
                    "ans":"privilleged"
                },
                {
                    "question":"Human rights was a theory of the UNO",
                    "opt1":"True",
                    "opt2":"False",
                    "opt3":"Maybe",
                    "opt4":"I don't know",
                    "ans":"True"
                },
                {
                    "question":"Participating in politics is a feature of popular participation",
                    "opt1":"True",
                    "opt2":"False",
                    "opt3":"Maybe",
                    "opt4":"I don't know",
                    "ans":"True"
                },
                {
                    "question":"What has to do with the sharing of power between the central government and other constituent units",
                    "opt1":"Centralization",
                    "opt2":"Decentralization",
                    "opt3":"Delegated Legislation",
                    "opt4":"Parliament Spread",
                    "ans":"Decentralization"
                }
                
            ]
        }
        
    ]
}
